lotsofjokes.com 2012-10-03

# Lots of Jokes - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Effective as of July 29, 2010**

This document explains the information Luckytool, LLC. (“Company”) may collect through our Web site at the Lots of Jokes web site (the “Services”) and how that information is used and shared. When you use the Services at Lots of Jokes, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us at privacy@lotsofjokes.com.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you use any of the Services we may ask you to provide us with the following types of information:

**Personal information you knowingly choose to disclose**

When you use any of the Services, you may be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, email address, gender and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us. We will store this information in a commercially reasonably secure environment. 

**Web site use information collected by us as you interact with the Services**

When you use any of the Services we may collect your browser type and IP address. This information may be gathered for all users of the Services, whether just visiting the Web site or actually using the Services. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. Should we have logins, then by default, we would use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to use the Services. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. When you use the Services, we may track the kinds of Services you use and how you used the Services. We may collect this information so that we can provide you the Services and offer personalized features.

**USE OF INFORMATION OBTAINED BY COMPANY**

  * We limit the sharing of information with others. We will upon your consent, using information you have provided, directly provide you with products and services that are related to or provide you added benefits of our Services. 

  * We may share the information we collect about you with other companies in order to provide you with access to products and services and to maintain your use of the Services effectively. We require these companies to use this information only for the limited purpose for which it was shared. We do not allow them to disclose it to others without our prior approval.

  * We may share the information we collect with our other corporate affiliates. Our corporate affiliates may offer a variety of products and services that can help you manage your finances or help protect against identity theft. We require these affiliates to use this information only for the limited purpose for which it was shared. We do not allow them to disclose it to others without our prior approval.

  * We may share the information we collect about you with other companies so that the Services you purchase are effectively provided. 

**Children Under Age 16**

The Lots of Jokes web site provides the Services to only those individuals aged 16 or older. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16 or knowingly allow such persons to register and/or use the Services. If you are under 16, please do not send any information about yourself to us – of ANY KIND. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at privacy@lotsojokes.com.

**Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18**

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

**Links**

The Lots of Jokes site may contain links or frames to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Company.

**Changing or Removing Information**

It is important that the information we maintain about you is accurate and complete. If you have reason to believe that we have information about you that is incomplete or inaccurate, please write to us at: PO Box 2789, Woodinville, Washington, 98072, USA or email us at privacy@lotsofjokes.com so that we can update this information.

**Security**

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the information we collect about you. Access to such information is restricted to individuals who need it in order to provide the Services to you. Employees who violate these confidentiality requirements are subject to our disciplinary process. Where third parties provide support services, we require them to conform to our privacy standards.

**Violations of this Policy**

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided to Company is a violation of the Company Terms of Use and should be reported to privacy@lotsofjokes.com.

**Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions**

If you choose to use any Company Services, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of and application of law of the state of Washington. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy’s effective date. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

**Contacting Company**

If you have further questions about our Privacy Policy please email those inquires to privacy@lotsofjokes.com.
